{"data":[{"question":"The movie was so ___ that all of the audience were _________ to tears.","a":"moving, moved","b":"moved, moving","c":"moved, moved","d":"moving, moving","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Moved: is a past participle. When used as an adjective it says how someone feels. \n- Moving: is a present participle. When used as an adjective it describes the people or things that cause the feelings ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"What the news said wasn't ___ at all.","a":"surprised","b":"surprising","c":"to surprise","d":"to be surprised","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Surprised: is a past participle. When used as an adjective it says how someone feels. \n- Surprising: is a present participle. When used as an adjective it describes the people or things that cause the feelings","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Everyone doesn't like ___.","a":"to insulted","b":"insulted","c":"insulting","d":"to be insulted","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Like to Verb: want to do sth \n- Passive voice: Like to be PP ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Before ___, the machines must be checked.","a":"having used","b":"using them","c":"being used","d":"use them","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Simple present tense \n- Before + Verb_ing","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Would you like ___ a cup of oolong tea?","a":"have","b":"to have","c":"had","d":"having","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Would you like + to Verb: suggestion, offer ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Rather than ___, Jonathan would choose to die.","a":"giving in","b":"to give in","c":"give in","d":"be giving in","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Rather than do sth: instead of","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"We'll never forget ___ Rome for the first time.","a":"visit","b":"to visit","c":"visited","d":"visiting","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Forget + V_ing: Forget something which have already happened\/done \n- Forget+ To Verb: Forget To do something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"There is nothing to do except ___ till it stops raining.","a":"waiting","b":"to wait","c":"waits","d":"wait","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Except sth\/do sth ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Stacy does nothing but ___.","a":"laugh","b":"to laugh","c":"being laughed","d":"to be laughed","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Somebody cannot but do something: used to say that someone has to do something or cannot stop themselves from doing it","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Instead of ___ sights, Edison would spend the time ___ in the public library.","a":"see, read","b":"seeing, reading","c":"seeing, to read","d":"to see, to read","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Instead of doing something\n- Spend time doing something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"}]}